When you open your heart...there's room for everyone.
Jesus Revolution is a drama, history film directed by Brent McCorkle.
In the 1970s, aimless teenager Greg Laurie searches for all the right things in all the wrong
places until he meets Lonnie Frisbee, a charismatic hippie/street preacher.
Together with local pastor Chuck Smith, they open the doors of
a languishing church to an unexpected revival.
Greg Laurie, played by Joel Courtney.
Chuck Smith, played by Kelsey Grammer.
Lonnie Frisbee, played by Jonathan Roumie.
Charlene, played by Kimberly Williams-Paisley.
Cathe Martin, played by Anna Grace Barlow.
Kay Smith, played by Julia Campbell.
Jesus Revolution is a 2023 American Christian drama film
directed by Jon Erwin and Brent McCorkle.
Based on the autobiographical book of the same name co-written by Greg Laurie, the film follows the teenage Laurie (Joel Courtney), Christian hippie Lonnie
Frisbee (Jonathan Roumie), and pastor Chuck Smith (Kelsey Grammer) as they take part in the Jesus movement in California during the late 1960s.
Anna Grace Barlow and Kimberly Williams-Paisley also star.
The film was theatrically released in the United
States by Lionsgate on February 24, 2023.
Although it received mixed reviews from critics, the film grossed $54
million worldwide against a production budget of $15 million.
The film explores themes of hippie, 1970s, based on true
story, aftercreditsstinger, southern california.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.